Nichole Alexandra Lischynski

ADDRESS TELEPHONE EMAIL

111 Greenwood Drive Moncton, NB, EIE 3B6 1 (902) 598 9777

4turtlesgirl123@gmail.com

I'm an ambitious and creative individual who values personal growth and interesting work. I've worked at a number of summer jobs since 2012 and am currently attending the two-year video game design and development program at Moncton's Eastern College.

EDUCATION

Three Oaks Senior High High School Diploma

Miscouche Consolidated Entrance into high school Summerside, Prince Edward Island September 2015 - June 2018

Miscouche, Prince Edward Island September 2006 - June 2015

WORK EXPERIENCE

Little Angels Daycare

Special Needs Assistant

Slemon Park, Prince Edward Island July 2018 - August 2018

- Duties: supervised children inside and outside in groups of up to fifteen, organized crafts and activities, tended to basic and emotional needs when necessary

Flore Store
Office Assistant

Souris, Prince Edward Island June 2018 - June 2018 June 2017 - August 2017

- Duties: filed and reorganized official store documents, created digital copies of handwritten documents and work history

Babysitting *Babysitter*

Souris, Prince Edward Island June 2012 - September 2017

- Duties: supervised children inside and outside, tended to basic and emotional needs when necessary, cleaned the house and yard when the time presented itself

Bluefin Restaurant

Busser

Souris, Prince Edward Island May 2014 - August 2014 June 2015 - August 2016

- Duties: cleaned and reset tables after each customer's use, occasionally tended to other tasks; washed dishes, served drinks and appetizers, took out the trash

Bayview Lodge Entertainment Hostess

Souris, Prince Edward Island July 2013 - August 2013

- Duties: hosted bingo and movie nights for the senior citizens of the Bayview Lodge twice a week

EXTRA-CURRICULAR / VOLUNTEER

Fandango Musical Harbourfront Theatre Assistant Prop Manager Summerside, Prince Edward Island November 2017 - December 2017

- Duties: obtained and prepared props for actors before and during plays, organized props

Yearbook Designer

January 2015 - May 2015

Miscouche Consolidated School

- Duties: took photos for yearbook use, created layout and designs for the final product

CERTIFICATIONS

High School Diploma

June 2018

Babysitting License

January 2012

REFERENCES

Jacqueline Aitken, self-employed, Souris, PE, (902) 969 1601 Carrie MacLellan, music teacher, Summerside, PE, (902) 888 8495, clmaclellan@edu.pe.ca David Jackson, florist/self-employed, Souris, PE, 1 (902) 969 8135, smidjackson@gmail.com